Guide to the Lewis L. Delafield, Eugene D. Hawkins and Affiliated Attorneys Records circa 1856-1921 (bulk, 1880s-1910) MS 157
New-York Historical Society
- Series II. Boxes labeled LLD (Louis L. Delafield), circa 1858-1909
  - LLD Packet 121, circa 1900-1906 (Offsite-box 41)
    3) Adaline E. Anderson et al v. Willam H. Maxwell (superintendent of city schools) et al, ca. 1904.
  - LLD Packet 122, circa 1903 (Offsite-box 41)
    Holds one matter: City of Ironwood [Michigan] v. William E. Coffin and Walter Stanton (partners), Malcolm Baxter Jr and Charles L. Hyde and Charles H. Jackson; and Thomas P. Wickes (receiver) re: dispute over municipal bonds, ca. 1903.
  - LLD Packet 123, circa 1899-1905 (Offsite-box 41)
    4 packets numbered 123:
    1) Title abstract of Charles Sooysmith to property between 109th and 110th streets, mortgaged to guardian Eliza(?) J. Shipman, ca. 1899.
    2) Application of William J. Goldey for writ of mandamus issued to William H. Maxwell (city schools superintendent) to place Goldey's name on eligibility list as principal of male schools, ca. 1901; and related People of the State of New York ex rel William J. Goldey v. William H. Maxwell
    4) Mercantile Trust Company (trustee) v. John W. Haddock et al, ca. 1905.
  - LLD Packet 124, circa 1897-1906 (Offsite-box 42)
    5 packets numbered 124:
    1) Morris K. Jesup v. Francis C. Travers et al, Richmond County, re: Beauty Isle Land Company, ca. 1904.
    2) Application of the Kingsbridge Railway Company for the appointment of commissioners, ca. 1901.
    3) Thomas Ewing Jr et al v. Sprague Electric Company, Westchester County, ca. 1906.
    4) Charles Metcalfe v. Vincent P. Travers et al, Richmond County, ca. 1905.
    5) Marie Dehais v. Etienne Sagnol, Tilly Sagnol, and Joseph Laemmle, ca. 1897.
  - LLD Packet 125, circa 1901-1903 (Offsite-box 42)
    3 packets numbered 125:
    1) People of the State of New York on the relation of John S. Sprague v. William H. Maxwell (city superintendent of schools), ca. 1903.
    2) Mary S. Van Winkle v. Elizabeth N. Van Winkle, Alexandra S. Hamilton, et al, ca. 1901-03.
    3) Uvalde Asphalt Paving Company v. New York City, ca. 1903.
  - LLD Packet 126, circa 1901 (Offsite-box 42)
    2 packets numbered 126:
    1) Roger F. Sturgis and Mildred Sturgis (wife) v. Charles I. Sturgis et al, ca. 1901.
    2) Gilbert W. Speir and Edmund L. Balies, executors of Robert Ray Hamilton estate v. Schuyler Van Cortlandt Hamilton et al, ca. 1901.
  - LLD Packet 128, circa 1873-1905 (Offsite-box 62)
    Holds 4 packets numbered 128:
    1) James R. O'Beirne for himself and other bondholders v. Spencer S. Bullis et al re: Allegheny & Kinzua Railroad Company, ca. 1905.
    2) Charles D. Leverich et al v. Matilda R.L. Bradford (administratrix of Matilda D. Leverich estate), et al, ca. 1903.
    3) Edgar J. Shipman v. Francis J. Schnugg, ca. 1899.
    4) Estate of John Markham matter.
    Also there are various loose papers. Matters include: William G. McRea v. The Mutual Bank, ca. 1901; George Ahrens v. Cornelia Ahrens et al, ca. 1901; Trustees of the Sailors' Snug Harbor v. Henry E. Ficken, ca. 1901; deed from Rufus Delafield to Nathaniel Prime and Edward Prime Jr, 1873; and some miscellaneous documents.
  - LLD Packet 129, circa 1890-1901 (Offsite-box 43)
    4 packets numbered 129:
    1) Amalia Kahn v. Manhattan Railway Company and Metropolitan Elevated Railroad Company, ca. 1901.
    2) Lawrence R. Jerome v. Lovell H. Jerome et al and Daniel Nason (executor), ca. 1899; and related matter against William Travers Jerome.
    3) Simson Wolf v. Manhattan Railway Company and Metropolitan Elevated Ralroad Company, ca. 1890.
    4) Settlement of accounts of Benigno Santos Suarez et al as executor of estate of Antonia Carrio de Sancho, ca. 1899.
  - LLD Packet 131, circa 1899-1905 (Offsite-box 43)
    6 packets numbered 131:
    1) Emily P. Delafield lease to Herman Schaus of 475 5th Ave, ca 1905.
    2) Committee of Bar Association's report of Surrogate's practice, ca. 1899.
    3) John B. Pine (trustee) v. Elizabeth Meyer et al, ca. 1899.
    4) Paul S. Bolger title to 17 and 19 Fairfield Place, Yonkers, Westchester County, ca. 1902-04.
    5) Charles Schekeler re: attempt to be eligible for teaching position, ca. 1903.
    6) Alvin H. Peckham lease to Schuyler Hamilton Jr, ca. 1903.
  - LLD Packet 132, circa 1902-1906 (Offsite-box 43)
    49 packets numbered 132. Most of these are single envelopes with few documents in them. Several of these are matters concerning members of the Delafield and Prime families. Packets with more documents are:
    1) NYC Interborough Railroad Company matter re: Riverdale property (agreement with John Kelvey and other matters), ca. 1903.
    2) Kemble property at Fort Lee, ca. 1902.
    3) Fanny Adele La Forge (a/k/a Frances Adele Brittain) will, ca. 1906.
    4) Annie S. Solger re: title of 42 Sunnyside Drive, Yonkers.
  - LLD Packet 133, circa 1903-1904 (Offsite-box 44)
    Entire packet concerns "An Act to provide for the erection of a Court House in the County of New York and authorizing the acquisition of a site therefor"; plus related amendments, etc, 1903-04.
  - LLD Packet 134, circa 1896-1903 (Offsite-box 44)
    4 matters:
    1) Florence Thayer Smith v. Arthur L.J. Smith, re: claim for support and education of their child Loughton Thayer Smith, ca. 1903.
    2) Hawkins & Delafield v. Marx, ca. 1893, with documents re: Lipman estate, ca. 1896.
    3) Elizabeth Kirby matter, ca. 1897.
    4) Harriet Abbott agreement with Catherine Anne Cuyler Abbott, ca. 1897.
  - LLD Packet 135, circa 1865-1909 (Offsite-box 44)
    Holds many matters with only a few documents each. The two most heavily documented matters are:
    1) Tallmadge Delafield v. Edgar S. Van Winkle, ca. 1875.
    2) Frank A.K. Boland matter, ca. 1909.
    Smaller sets of documents include, perhaps among others:
    * William B. Astor to Laura A. Delano et al (deed of trust), 1865.
    * Judiciary Committee of the Bar Association, ca. 1907 matters. Statement of LLD of his judicial campaign expense, 1906.
    * Wendel estate re: Elevated Railroad station on 6th Ave at 37th Street.
    * A.C. Dana re: lease, 1906.
    * Emily P. Delafield re: sale to William E. Dodge, ca. 1892.
    * Delafield property in New Orleans.
    * Helene Fitter and John Laue v. Edward Moroney et al.
    * Joy, Langdon & Company partnership agreement.
    * Franklin B. Lord and Lucius H. Beers (trustees for Laura A. Delano) v. Henry J. McGuckin et al, re: estate of Julius Lipman, ca. 1900.
    * Ruth Mackey title re: 57 East 120th Street.
    * Andrew J. Smith v. American Museum of Natural History, ca. 1903.
    * Arthur C. Train re: judgeship, ca. 1907.
    * Carolyn Archer Dana will, 1907.
    * Elizabeth Jarvis Dana will, 1907.
    * Anne S. Delafield will, 1907.
    * Howard Duffield will, 1907.
    * Mary Kihm will, 1909.
    * Charlotte G. Wyeth will, 1906.
  - LLD Packet 136, circa 1906-1907 (Offsite-box 45)
    Entire packet concerns the application of the Title Guaranty and Trust Company of Scranton, Pennsylvania to make and file a statement of its condition and an examination thereof as provided by Ch. 720 of the Laws of 1893, as amended, Erie County, ca. 1906-07, with financial statements, etc.
  - LLD Packet 137, circa 1870-1898 (Offsite-box 45)
    This packet primarily holds loose documents related to miscellaneous matters. The documents include, among others, tax and water bill receipts on various properties, including in Riverdale, 1870-90s; property insurance policies; and small packets of bonds/mortgages and agreements, several of them related to the Delafields, 1880s-90s. The largest set of documents in this packet relate to a matter concerning subscribers to U.S. war bonds, ca. 1898.
  - LLD Packet 138, circa 1900-1908 (Offsite-box 45)
    The entire packet concerns Georgiana G.R. Wendel (alleged incompetent) v. John G. Wendel and Rebecca A.D. Wendel (executors of John D. Wendel estate), Westchester and New York County, ca. 1900-08.
  - LLD Packet 139, circa 1900-1904 (Offsite-box 45)
    Packet holds 5 principal matters:
    1) Zax K. Berlin re: title to 349-351 East 17th Street, ca. 1901.
    2) Innes v. Manhattan Railway Company and Connoly v. Manhattan Railway Company.
    3) Title of Simon Jacobs to property on 9th Street at 2nd Ave, ca. 1900.
    4) B. Aymar Sands and Samuel P. Blagden Jr v. Lawrence M. Kortright et al.
    5) Title to Maurice Myers of 282 and 284 Stanton Street, New York City, ca. 1901.
    The packet also holds miscellaneous property/title related papers, such as Jacob Schattman/100th Street, ca. 1902; and leasehold estate of David I. Seiffer at Sailor's Snug Harbor, ca. 1904.
  - LLD Packet 140, circa 1894 (Offsite-box 46)
    Entire packet concerns Charles L. Hyde and Charles H. Jackson v. City of Ironwood, Michigan, ca. 1894.
  - LLD Packet 141, circa 1875-1894 (Offsite-box 46)
    Packet holds 5 matters: 1) Malcolm Baxter Jr v. City of Ironwood, Michigan, ca. 1894. 2) Hampton Water Company matter, ca. 1890. 3) Frederick Prime will, 1875. 4) Augustus Van Cortlandt lease to Thomas B. Veeder. 5) William C. Dodge matter re: sewer at Riverdale.
  - LLD Packet 142, circa 1900-1908 (Offsite-box 46)
    Packet holds 8 matters:
    1) Thick packet of "miscellaneous matters of Emily P. Delafield," ca. 1901-06.
    2) Thick packet re: Schuyler Hamilton estate matters, ca. 1903.
    3) Alpine Club of Canada documents (slender packet, appears to relate to a personal, not legal, matter).
    4) Matter of Robert H. Delafield with Pacific Packing & Navigation Company, ca. 1904.
    5) Bella Butler v. George W. Perkins, ca. 1906.
    6) Adelheit Niemeier re: property appraisals, ca. 1901.
    7) John H. Pugh re: Sweetser estate, ca. 1900.
    8) Bringhurst re: title at 145 West 73rd Street, ca. 1908.
  - LLD Packets 143, 144, circa 1887-1889 (Offsite-box 47)
    Both of these packets concern the matter Maturin L. Delafield v. Clarence Delafield et al, re: dispute over estate property, ca. 1887-1889.
  - LLD Packet 145, circa 1887 (Offsite-box 47)
    The entire packet concerns Charles B. Fosdick et al (executors of Henry Delafield estate) v. Maturin L. Delafield et al, ca. 1887.
  - LLD Packet 146, circa 1887 (Offsite-box 48)
  - LLD Packet 147, 1876-1879 (Offsite-box 48)
    The entire packet holds printed material only for Clinton G. Colgate v. Western Union Telegraph Company, US Circuit Court, Southern District of New York, re: patent, 1878; and Arthur M. Eastman v. Western Union Telegraph Company, defendant's testimony, US Circuit Court, Southern District of New York, 1876. Also, related to the cases, a "specimen of cables & gutta percha, 1879."
  - LLD Packet 147a, circa 1877-1901 (Offsite-box 48)
    1) Julia F. Baldwin (administrator of Susan Baldwin estate) v. Caroline E. Trowbridge et al, Chancery of New Jersey, ca. 1901.
    2) People ex rel Elizabeth C. Jay (landlord) v. William H. Bennett, et al (tenants) and Henry Dralle et al (under-tenants), ca. 1877-78.
  - LLD Packet 148, circa 1892-1902 (Offsite-box 62)
    The entire bundle concerns the matter of accounts of Annie R. Prime as guardian of Charlotte H. Prime (infant), and related accounts of Francis T. Garretson as executor of Charlotte W. Prime estate, ca. 1892-1902.
  - LLD Packet 149, circa 1895-1909 (Offsite-box 48)
    Holds 10 matters:
    1) Robert Hare Delafield estate, ca. 1906.
    2) Harriet Prime Gibbons estate.
    3) Ella Willing Jackson will, ca. 1905.
    4) Reginald Jevons estate, ca. 1908.
    5) Receipt of Gouverneur Kemble for participation certificates of Knickerbocker Trust Company.
    6) Henry La Forge will and related documents re: Elizabeth La Forge, ca. 1905.
    7) David H. McAlpin will and related documents, including incorporation of McAlpin Realty Company, ca. 1907.
    8) Margaret Walton Pellew will, ca. 1909.
    9) Hannah Pizer re: title to 329 East 50th Street, ca. 1895.
    10) Charlotte G. Wyeth will, ca. 1909.
  - LLD Packets 150, 150b, circa 1898-1908 (Offsite-box 49)
    The bulk of these packets relate to various matters concerning Elizabeth Shipley Smith, especially re: the estate of John Galt Smith for which she is the trustee. These matters include Elizabeth Shipley Smith v. George Kennedy Smith, ca. 1908, and Smith v. Florence K. Williamson, ca. 1899. (A related set of documents from packet 152 was also placed in this box.) Packet 150 also includes documents re: amending the "Act relating to state charities," ca. 1900.
  - LLD Packets 151, 152, 155, circa 1906-1908 (Offsite-box 50)
    Packet 151 holds the matter of justification as to solvency for the Metropolitan Surety Company, ca. 1906, and for the People's Surety Company of New York, ca. 1907. Packet 152 holds the same matter for the United Surety Company, ca. 1908. Packet 155 holds the same matter for the Bankers Surety Company, ca. 1906-07, and for the Aetna Indemnity Company, ca. 1906.
  - LLD Packet 153, 1903-1908 (Offsite-box 50)
    1) Myer Hellman v. Stephen Farrelly (receiver for City Trust Safe Deposit & Surety Company of Philadelphia), ca. 1907.
    2) Dennett Surpassing Coffee Company v. Alfred C. Hirsh, Walter A. Hirsh and Otto J. Lang, ca. 1903.
    3) Eustis L. Hopkins re: Larchmont Roadhouse, ca. 1908.
  - LLD Packets 154, 156, 157, circa 1899-1908 (Offsite-box 51)
    Packet 154 holds two matters: 1) Justification as to solvency for the American Bonding Company of Baltimore, Maryland, ca. 1907; and 2) Catharine M. Forde v. New York City re: New York School Teachers Association matters; other plaintiffs in related matters are Magnus Gross and Anna I. Mathews, ca. 1899-1900.
    Packet 156 holds 3 matters concerning justifications as to solvency for the Federal Union Surety Company of Indiana, ca. 1906; Empire State Surety Company of Brooklyn, NY, ca. 1907; and American Surety Company of New York, ca. 1906.
    Packet 157 holds 2 matters concerning justifications as to solvency for the Illinois Surety Company, ca. 1906; and for the Massachusetts Bonding & Insurance Company, ca. 1908.
  - LLD Packet 158, circa 1906-1907 (Offsite-box 52)
    The entire packet concerns the justification as to solvency for the National Surety Company, ca. 1906-07.
  - LLD Packet 159, circa 1890-1895 (Offsite-box 52)
    Holds 5 matters:
    1) Orchard Irrigation Company of Idaho matters, ca. 1892-94.
    2) Peninsula Water Company matters, ca. 1894.
    3) Toppan Manufacturing Company matters (other names here: Charles Toppan, DeWitt Smith, Henry Fletcher Godfrey, Edith Godfrey Hyde, etc., ca. 1895.
    4) Idaho Fruit Company matters, ca. 1894.
    5) Charles L. Hyde v. Alfred H. Harrison, ca. 1890-93.
    There are also a few miscellaneous loose papers.
  - LLD Packet 160, circa 1903-1905 (Offsite-box 52)
    1) Bundle of "miscellaneous matters" concerning bankers Hyde & Jackson.
    2) Helen Villard Bell v. Fanny Garrison Villard, the American Museum of Natural History, et al, Westchester County, ca. 1903.
    3) Bowling Green Trust Company v. City Trust, Safe Deposit and Surety Company of Philadelphia, ca. 1905.
  - LLD Packet 161, circa 1903-1905 (Offsite-box 53)
    Entire packet concerns the matter of the application of New York City to acquire real estate under Ch 712 of the Laws of 1901 for construction of a terminal on the westerly or Manhattan end of the New York and Brooklyn Bridge. Related matters here are Frances J. Storms and Alfred Storms v. Manhattan Railway Company and the New York Elevated Railroad Company. Other surnames involved in these matters are Johnston, Hanover, Schmidt, etc.; ca. 1903-05.
  - LLD Packets 163, 164, circa 1906-1907 (Offsite-box 53)
    Both of these packets concern W. Irving Clark and Caroline L. Iselin (executors of Charlotte M. Goodridge estate) v. Frederick G. Goodridge, Charlotte G. Wyeth, et al, ca. 1906-1907.
  - LLD Packet 165, circa 1906-1907 (Offsite-box 54)
    The entire packet continues the matter of W. Irving Clark and Caroline L. Iselin (executors of Charlotte M. Goodridge estate) v. Frederick G. Goodridge, Charlotte G. Wyeth, et al, ca. 1906-1907.
  - LLD Packet 166, circa 1907 (Offsite-box 54)
    1) Andrew Henri Hart v. William W. Miller et al, Kings County, ca. 1907. Other related matters here as well (Katharine Evans Mairs v. David Lewis Evans; agreement with Robert W. De Forest; deed for the Swedish Evangelical Lutheran Bethlehem Church, etc.).
    2) Matters concerning the Perry Hunt Holding Corporation, Willard W. Hunt, George Chapman, and the Gillette Sales Company, ca. 1907.
    3) Willett G. Smith v. R. Dickinson Jewett, ca. 1907.
    4) Lemuel D. Lilly v. John A McCall and George W. Perkins.
  - LLD Packets 168, 168a, circa 1906 (Offsite-box 54)
    Both packets hold Hudson & Manhattan Railroad Company v. Katharine Jackson, Josephine J.S. Wendel, Emil P. Birnbaum, Graton & Knight Manufacturing Company, and the Frasse Company, et al, ca. 1906.
  - LLD Packets 169, 170, circa 1903-1907 (Offsite-box 55)
    The entire packet 169 concerns New York Central & Hudson River Railroad Company v. Susan F. Colgate et al, Westchester County, ca. 1907. Packet 170 holds two matters, one of which continues the NYC & HR Railroad v. Colgate matter. The second matter in 170 is Sarah May Le Brantz v. William G. Conklin (executor of Sarah Ann Waters estate) and American Female Guardian Society and Home for the Friendless of New York City, et al, ca. 1903.
  - LLD Packet 171, circa 1905-1908 (Offsite-box 55)
    The packet holds several matters, one of which has extensive documentation: Robert E. Robinson v. New York, Westchester & Boston Railway Company, et al, ca. 1908. The other matters in this packet hold only a few documents each:
    1) Redington v. Hartford, ca. 1907.
    2) George W. Perkins re: Riverdale dock.
    3) Susan B. Sturgis property lease re: 80 & 81 South Street.
    4) Application of Oscar H. Vaupel to sell real estate from the estate of Frederick W. Fenner, a lunatic, ca. 1905.
    5) Accounts of Grant Squires and George A. Wells, executors of Henry M. Wells estate, ca. 1908.
    There are also a few other small miscellaneous matters.
  - LLD Packet 171, circa 1908 (Offsite-box 62)
    Printed material re: Robert E. Robinson v. New York, Westchester & Boston Railway Company, et al, ca. 1908.
- Series III. Boxes labeled H-D (Hawkins-Delafield), circa 1853-1924 (bulk 1880s-1910)
  The series holds the content of boxes originally labeled as H-D. It includes files of Hawkins and Delafield and the short-lived Hawkins, Delafield and Sturgis. The principals are Lewis Livingston Delafield II, Eugene Hawkins, and Robert Sturgis, with some files of Dexter Hawkins, Caleb Burbank, and a few Lewis Delafield I.
  Some notable matters in this series: business disputes, including those concerning the firms Clapp & Co. and Price, McCormick & Co.; various claims against the Manhattan Railway Company and Metropolitan Elevated Railroad Company; and legal work for the Meeks family. Matters concerning the estate of Wilhelm Pickhardt are extensively documented with original correspondence, financial records, etc. concerning Pickhardt's patents, property in Schroon Lake, business dealings, etc. Also extensively documented is Caleb Burbank's work as executor for the will of his uncle, Ambrose Burbank, and the resulting long-running lawsuit of Mary Newcomb, David Newcomb, and others against Caleb.
  The series holds some case diaries and other personal papers of the attorneys. Some of these pertain to Robert Sturgis. He seems to have had some involvement or investment with the Nicaragua Canal Company; this series (and series V) have various printed material related to the canal from Sturgis's files.
  The documents in this series were originally held in about 180 boxes labeled as H-D, with each label also indicating a number or numbers ranging from 1 to 675, with gaps. Each number represented a packet of documents in the original box. Unlike the D-L and LLD boxes, with only a few exceptions each number related to only one packet and that packet related to only one matter. The container list retains this sequence, with some exceptions to accommodate storage considerations.
  - H-D Bundles #1-20, circa 1879-1899 (Offsite-box 56)
    1) Mary Day v. New York Elevated Railroad Company et al, ca. 1893.
    2 & 10) Samuel T. Hubbard et al v. Frank J. Currie (and related matter against William F. Croft), ca. 1895.
    3) Wilson Godfrey and Ralph E. Sumner v. William B. Walsh (doing business as Syracuse & Oswego Line), ca. 1888-90.
    4) Arthur Tooth et al v. Thomas Gilbert, ca. 1879.
    5) James H. Goodsell matters, ca. 1892.
    6) Marcus L. Freeman et al v. William S. Darling.
    7) Theodore H. Price et al v. John Grant Lyman, ca. 1896.
    8) Frank M. Gillett et al v. William I. Whiting, ca. 1885.
    9) Louis Solomon v. New York Cedar War Company, ca. 1887.
    11) Elizabeth Fullagar v. William E. Fullagar, et al, Kings County, ca. 1884.
    12) Ball-Warren Commission Company v. Ozro W. Clapp and Dwight O. Clapp (Clapp & Co.), ca. 1897.
    13) Malcolm Baxter Jr v. Ozro W. Clapp and Dwight O. Clapp (Clapp & Co.), ca. 1897.
    14) William Custer v. Greenpoint Ferry Company, Brooklyn City Court, ca. 1884.
    15) Robert Forbes v. Charles P. Sullivan, ca. 1891.
    16) [Small bundle with few documents, not identified by archivist]
    17) Annie M. McEvoy v. Florence Kirk, et al, Kings County, ca. 1895.
    18) Matters re: Catharine Vidal estate, Westchester County, ca. 1899.
    19) American Encaustic Tiling Company, Ltd v. Allan McLane et al, ca. 1882.
    20) Frederick L. Gilbert v. James L. Libby, ca. 1888.
  - H-D Bundles #22-47, circa 1878-1897 (Offsite-box 57)
    22) Sedgwick City Bank of Sedgwick, Kansas v. John H. Meyer, and against Ernest F. Hoenig, U.S. Circuit Court, Southern District of New York.
    24) Dissolution of the Colorado Land and Mineral Company, ca 1886.
    25) Ira H. Randall v. Ozro W. Clapp and Dwight O. Clapp (Clapp & Co.)
    26) Joseph W. Meeks Jr v. Albert V. Meeks et al, Suffolk County, ca. 1887.
    27) Josiah H. Bertine v. New York Elevated Railroad Company et al, ca. 1891.
    28) Catharine Moran v. James O'Neil and Mary Ann O'Neil, ca. 1886.
    29) Samuel T. Hubbard et al v. N. Schwab, ca. 1894-95.
    30) Mary E. Thuries v. Albert N. Thuries, re: divorce and alimony, ca. 1882.
    31) Accounts of Henry L. Day as executor of Titus Webb estate, ca. 1884
    32) Application of Arthur P. Quimby and Orville J. Quimby to sell real estate for a minor, Arthur P. Quimby, ca. 1898.
    34) Hermann Weiller v. Emanuel Bernhardt and Lena Kopetzky, ca. 1893.
    35) Settlement of accounts of Margaretta De Forest, administratrix of Benjamin L. De Forest estate, ca. 1885-89.
    36) Elizabeth Van Anda v. New Albany Banking Company, ca. 1893.
    37) Malcolm Alexander et al v. Schooner "D.M. Anthony," U.S. District Court, Southern District of New York, ca. 1895.
    38) George L. Lemon v. Ozro W. Clapp and Dwight O. Clapp (Clapp & Co.), ca. 1897.
    39) John G. Moore v. Sarah H. Aldrich et al, and related matters re: estate of Jane A. Moore, ca. 1892.
    40) Caroline Converse v. New York Elevated Railroad Company and Manhattan Railway Company; also Elizabeth M. Blague v. the railroad companies, ca. 1891-92.
    43) Donald McQuinn v. James Farmer, ca. 1878.
    44) John C. Griswold v. Charles H. Botsford, ca. 1891; and related agreements with Botsford and with Roberta Sharkey, ca. 1891.
    45) Hermann Weiller v. Emanuel Bernhardt et al, ca. 1893.
    46) Samuel S. Howland et al v. Louisa M. Howland et al, ca. 1884.
    47) Elizabeth M. Blague will and estate matters, ca. 1892.
  - H-D Bundles #48-65, circa 1874-1899 (Offsite-box 58)
    48) Newton E. Whiteside et al v. Noyac Cottage Association, ca. 1892.
    49) Elizabeth Fullagar v. William E. Fullagar, et al, Kings County, ca. 1884.